Front-end Developer / Japan Fukuoka, Fukuoka

Profile

I am working as a web designer/developer after completing a web design course at a school specializing in creator training. Currently, I am in charge of the front end of application development using UE4, standing between designers and engineers to ensure efficient application development.

Experience

August 2015 - February 2016 | Kyusyu Intermedia Lab | Web Designer

Responsible for creating banners mainly for streaming service and designing and coding corporate websites.

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript Coding
- Banner Image Design

February - March 2016 | Fukuhaku Sogo Printing | Web Developer

Responsible for UI implementation of web application

HTML/CSS/JavaScript Coding

April 2016 - June 2018 | Vega corporation at Sales Department | Web Deigner/Developer

Responsible for EC site maintenance and operation, LP page design/coding.

- HTML/CSS/JavaScript Coding
- Banner Image Design

July 2018 - Present | Vega corporation at R&D Department | 3D Creator/Front-end Developer

I was in charge of 3D modeling and UI development of the application, and I proposed improvements to the application functions in terms of usability and accessibility.

- 3D Modeling for AR
- Development Application Using Unreal Engine4
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript Coding

Languages/Tools

HTML/CSS/JavaScript(p5.js,Three.js,webpack,Express,Next.js,Gatsby.js)/TypeScript Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator/Xd/Figma/Blender/Unreal Engine4/Git/Github

Education

December 2014 - August 2015 Diploma of Web Design Course, Digital Hollywood Studio October 2020 - Present Bachelor of Computer Science, University of London